(Sheldon:)Oh, dear.
(Sheldon:)Penny, have you been recording
shows on our DVR again?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Answer honestly. This is not a trial.
That will come later.
(Penny:)Absolutely not.
(Penny:)Help me out here.
I can't afford another demerit.
Uh, maybe we were hacked. The Chinese
have been hacking everything lately.
Why would the Chinese make our DVR
record Paul Blart: Mall Cop?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)It's a fat guy on a Segway.
That's funny everywhere.
- I'm deleting it.
- Hang on.
(Penny:)Maybe the Chinese
haven't finished watching it yet.
(Leonard:)If you're trying to make space on the DVR...
...why don't you get rid of stuff
you've already watched? Like Alphas.
No, that's the season-two finale.
Quite the cliffhanger.
I'm gonna rewatch it
before season three starts.
There's no season three.
They canceled that show.